Celia Noriega

Phone: (714) 261-0099 | Email: noriegacelia2124@gmail.com | Santa Ana, CA 92704

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/celianoriega/

GitHub: https://github.com/CeliaNoriega Portfolio: https://celianoriega.github.io/

Summary

Front end web developer utilizing my background in customer service to build a more user friendly experience on the web. Earned a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of California, Irvine. Flexible and motivated team member with strong communication skills and a focus on mobile-first design and development.

Technical Skills

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL **Applications:** MySQL, MongoDB, GitHub, Heroku

Tools: React, Query, Node, Handlebars, Bootstrap, Material-ui, Express, Sequelize

Projects

Soy Tofu | https://github.com/CeliaNoriega/Soy Tofu | https://soy-tofu-ca.herokuapp.com/

- Summary: (In progress) A fully functioning restaurant page with admin user authentication and online ordering.
- Role: Front End Developer
- Technologies: React, Material-ui, MongoDB, Axios, Express, Heroku

Fitness Edge | https://github.com/ron-est/Fitness-Edge | https://fitnessedge.herokuapp.com/

- Summary: Plan a whole week of workouts with our workout planner.
- Role: Front End Developer
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, Materialize, Dragula, Express, Workbench, MySQL

Travel-19 | https://github.com/ky-lore/Travel-19 | https://ky-lore.github.io/Travel-19/

- Summary: Travel website that notifies you of current covid-stats for city searched.
- Role: Front End Developer
- Technologies: HTML, Javascript, Bulma CSS Framework, Ajax, APIs.

Education

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development — *University of California, Irvine Division of Continuing Education* — Irvine, CA

Diploma — Valley High School — Santa Ana, CA

Experience

Nordstrom, Newport Beach, CA — *Logistics Associate* November 2019 - October 2020

Disneyland Resort, Anaheim, CA — *Cast Member* January 2018- January 2019

AMC Theatres, Irvine, CA — *Crew Lead*June 2016- December 2017